Sinclair Browning Papers, 1942-2009 (bulk 1997-2000)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 11: Feathers Brush My Heart 2, 1998-2013
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1998-2013
    - Story Submission, Meyer, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Story Submission, Miller, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Story Submission, Miroglotta, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Story Submission, Monocchi, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Story Submission, Monthan, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Story Submission, Natiello, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Story Submission, Paquin, E, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Story Submission, Paquin, R, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Story Submission, Peterson, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Story Submission, Phillippi Walls, 2003-2012 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Story Submission, Plog, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Story Submission, Pullen, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Story Submission, Quann, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Story Submission, Reed, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Story Submission, Revez, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Story Submission, Robbins, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Story Submission, Roberts, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Story Submission, Romanello, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Story Submission, Russian, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Story Submission, Schlesinger, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Story Submission, Schmidt, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Story Submission, Sinclair, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Story Submission, Smith, Mona, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Story Submission, Smith, Turalee, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Story Submission, Speight, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Story Submission, Stahura, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Story Submission, Stocken, 2002-2013 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Story Submission, Terryviale, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Story Submission, Timmermon, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Story Submission, Toledo, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Story Submission, Turner, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Story Submission, Vennard, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Story Submission, Weyer, 2005-2012 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Story Submission, Whitey, 2011-2013 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Story Submission, Woodruf, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Series 12: Other Writings, 1968-2003
  This series contains the various materials created by Browning that were not novels, including short fiction, articles for horse journals, and screenplays. In addition, there are essays written by Browning for an English class that she attended at the University of Arizona.
  - Subseries 1: Classes Taught, undated
    This subseries contains the handouts and outlines created for writing workshops that Browning taught.
    - Historical Novel Workshop, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Novel Workshop Handouts, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2: Fiction, 1988-2000
    This subseries contains various published and unpublished short stories written by Browning.
    - Faraway Monograph, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - House of Joy, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Chapters, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Research, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Susan Parker, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Pretty Horses, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Unpublished Patricia Story, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Vulture Story, 23 April 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 3: Non Fiction, 1968-2005
    This subseries contains nonfiction articles and essays written by Browning. Also included are articles written about Browning’s personal and professional life.
    - Articles about Browning (Folder 1 of 2), circa 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Articles about Browning (Folder 2 of 2), circa 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Benjamin's Day at Mercado, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Books That Had an Influence on Me, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - English Class Essays, circa 1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Ms. Timmy, Mr. Westmoreland, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - One Every Minute, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Outline as an Afterthought, July 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Published Articles (Folder 1 of 2), 1988-2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Published Articles (Folder 2 of 2), 1988-2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Published Horse Articles, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Santa Fean, Mystery Excerpt, March 2002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Shoofly, Who Records the Cowboy Way, June 1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Stranger in My House, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 4: Poetry, undated
    This subseries contains unpublished poetry written by Browning for her English class at the University of Arizona.
    - English Class, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 5: Screenplays, 1980-2003
    This subseries contains unpublished screenplays written by Browning. 8 Martini Nights was written as a collaboration with Mary Tate Engels.
    - 8 Martini Nights (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 8 Martini Nights (FOlder 2 of 2), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - The Camp Grant Affair, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Paper Roses, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - The Stockholm Syndrome, May 1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 6: Speeches, 2003
    This subseries contains copies of the speeches that Browning was invited to give at various conferences and school events.
    - Fighting over the B Word...One Writer's Journey, 21 April 2003 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Sonoran Science Academy, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - My Mystery Writing, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Mystery and Suspense Writing at the Society of Southwestern Writers, 25 January 2003 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Unlocking the Secrets to Mystery Writing, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)